Perhaps I'll set up here tonight.
This'll do.
I can't sleep...
All because I drank coffee in the evening.
I told you not to.
But it's cool.
What's that?
What's that guy doing here?
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
My heart is racing like crazy
And right before my eyes
Are the colors of a brand new world
Whoa
Stay with me today
We'll walk hand in hand
Dreaming of the place where we can become light
I can hear the magic
I wanna sing with you
Let's sing together
You're a bright shining star
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
We can be shining stars
Forever and ever
That's our secret magic
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
B-U-B-E-E, bubee
Bubee love
You're Invited to Felix Star
Fuu-chan, bye-bye!
See you tomorrow!
So sleepy...
Wonder what that was last night.
What do you mean?
You saw him too, Uguisu.
He was in the garden, all glittery.
Glittery?
You don't remember?
Maybe I was just half-asleep.
I'm home!
He is there!
The man from last night...
Oh my!
Good day to you.
I take it you reside here?
Yes, I do...
So, what are you doing in our garden?
It's a beautiful garden,
so I figured I'd help myself.
Oh, thank you... wait, no!
You can't come in here without asking!
I came in here assuming
it was home to fellow magic beings,
but you appear to be human.
Yet I can sense a twinkle of magic power.
Huh? No way! There's no magic power here at all!
Rest easy. I come from Felix Star.
There's no trouble if citizens
of the magical land find out.
Really?
I'm Nonoyama Fuu. What's your name?
My name is Piyopiyon Ponporone Nyororond VI.
That's a real mouthful...
Hey, so... I was given magic power,
but I can't get it to work right.
Do you know why?
Well, there's many different kinds of magic.
Take this, for example.
This type of spell should be simple enough.
Amazing...
I know!
Sir, please become my magic teacher!
Your teacher?
Yeah! I wanna get better at using magic!
Hmm, I'm not quite sure...
It'll be perfect! Pretty please!
Fine, then.
Really?!
Yay!
Well, then. Let's be off.
Off? To where?
This is not a place fit to learn about magic.
We must head to the magical land.
Wait, right now?
But I was told not to go too far...
It's Felix Star!
Yay, I'm going home!
Uguisu!
Hey, wait!
Hurry along now.
Come on!
I'm home.
I have to hurry.
Goodbye!
What are you doing today?
I'm recording an audition video
at the agency.
"Attention, please!"
Cute!
Excuse me.
Do you have a moment?
Y-Yes.
This person seems suspicious...
Are they from the magical land?
I'm looking for directions.
Do you know the way to this place
called Café Dubdub?
I'm meeting a friend there.
The café next door to the agency...
I'm going to the area, so I'll guide you there.
You will? Thanks a ton!
I heard their panini are super good!
Is that so?
The cheese is so melty.
Do you go there often?
No, not really.
I see...
Here we are.
Ah, yep, this is the place! Thanks!
Well, I'll be off now...
Wait up.
I'll treat you for helping me out!
It's fine! I have somewhere to be...
No need to be so humble!
I'm not!
This is the magical land,
Felix Star!
What do you wanna get to eat?
Lemme think.
What is this place?
It feels so nostalgic.
Nice fresh air!
Hold on a minute! What of our magic lesson?
Oh, right!
Now, let us begin.
Okay!
Eggs?
They're for magic training.
Beginners start with these.
Huh...
Use magic to turn this into something you like.
Okay.
Lililula, palilula.
O egg, become a cake!
So exciting!
I messed up.
Hmm, you're not quite casting it right.
It's as if you're grabbing an eel
then letting it slip through your hands.
Really?
It's important for you to be focused
when making a wish.
When casting magic, you shouldn't go after eels.
You must try to catch something bigger, like fried shrimp.
Got it.
Now, give it another try.
Lililula, palilula.
O egg, become chocolate!
Yay, Kabappy!
That's not chocolate.
Oh, right. I guess I messed up after all.
Perhaps it's too cramped here
to give you the right motivation.
I know a better place up ahead,
so let's give it a try there.
Hey, can you make the lesson
easier to understand?
Now, you're not too bad.
After all, most humans can't use magic at all.
You can because you have strong feelings inside.
I have... strong feelings...
Why is this happening...?
Wow, this place is pretty neat.
I have somewhere to be...
Good afternoon!
Welcome in!
Yo, been a while!
Coming in.
You look well.
Meeter?
Oh, fancy seeing you here!
Which means you must be...
Meeter-san?
Nice to meet you. I'm Lulu.
Azuki's told me all about you.
I loved your last TV performance.
Thank you very much...
for the power I have now.
Hey, you two know each other?
I'm the cat here!
Can I take your order?
A magical juice and a fried combo juice.
Oh, and a black tea.
And panini for the whole table!
You got it.
Three sugar cubes for the black tea, then.
Um, what brings you here, Meeter-san?
I'm here to meet him.
So, how are the preparations coming along?
Well, the committee's reached out
to a bunch of folks,
but none of them have really stuck out to us.
Have you picked out a venue?
We have a few places in mind.
Wanted to get your thoughts on the options.
What are they talking about?
I don't know.
Thank you for waiting!
Oh, here it comes!
Here's your black tea.
Thank you!
Don't hang around weird people like this.
You'll make me worried.
N-No, I got forced into... this...
Let's eat!
Um...
This tastes great!
What is this place?
The magic mountain.
I figure it's a great spot for training.
Many people around here
go hiking up this mountain.
There's even taller mountains around it.
This one is better.
The trailhead's just up here.
Hello!
Kids cannot enter.
Aw, what?
Oh, I forgot. That'll complicate things.
I can get in if I'm a grown-up, right?
Litto!
Lililula, palilula!
Pam pam power!
How's this?
What a surprise!
You're Lilly the idol?
Clearly your transformation magic is impeccable.
You know about me?
You don't see magical idols often,
so you're famous in this land.
I had no idea!
You can pass.
Thanks!
Let us climb.
Okay!
Here we are.
This is the summit!
That was fast.
I'm beat.
Now, let us get right to training.
What spell would you like to learn next?
The other day, I got into a fight with my big sis.
Are there any good spells for that?
The best remedy for a fight
is for both sides to apologize.
It's the most effective spell there is.
Spoken like a real teacher!
Hey, is that Lilly?
It is! It's Lilly the idol!
Wow, so cool!
I saw you on TV!
What are you in the magical land for?
Sing for us!
Uh, now's not a good time.
Now, now. Lilly has magic training to get to.
Sorry!
Lilly!
Aw, man!
Oh, Lilly! Don't go that way!
Huh?
Are you alright?
Huh? Where has she gone to?
Ouch...
Huh?
Where am I?
Wake up, Uguisu!
What is it?
I tripped and fell into some weird place.
Huh?
We have to get back to the teacher.
How?
I don't know...
but let's get moving.
I'm scared... Let's leave...
That's literally what we're doing!
About the venue,
how does a limestone cave sound?
Wouldn't a plateau be better?
Plateaus have stronger winds.
But a cave would be too small.
Good point...
Um, I really should be...
There's gotta be something
to help us decide.
I know just the thing!
Ms. Manager!
Mind if we go to the basement?
Huh? That's fine.
We want to hear your thoughts too!
Go!
Um, thank you for the meal!
I have to go!
Wait!
What were those two doing?
Let's go to work.
Did you want to use the TV?
Yeah.
Oh, so this is what the basement looks like.
Normally only regulars are allowed in here.
I'll turn it on.
Ooh, I like the look of that!
Let's see a plateau.
I think this is better.
Nah, the cave still beats that.
No way! Why is Lilly there?
I have an urgent matter,
so please watch the store for me!
What?
Lilly... Fuu...
Why are you in the magical land?
Fuu, wait for me!
Is anyone there?
Hello! Anyone?!
Why?
There were so many people around before...
Where'd they all go?
Hey, let's go home already.
I want to go home too, you know.
This way.
Are you sure?
I can't believe she came here...
That mountain...
If a human goes into the holy land
deep in its forest, it'll cause a lot of trouble.
The "no entry" sign was knocked over...
She really is in here.
I have to get her out safely,
or Shio will be mad at me.
Are we really going the right way?
I don't know.
I thought the magic world
would be a lot more fun.
It is fun!
Is anyone there?!
Lilly!
She's this way!
There's no one here... This is bad...
Now what?
Uguisu, do something.
No, you do something.
Oh, right!
The egg my teacher gave me!
Lililula, palilula,
o egg, get us out of this forest!
It's so warm.
So pretty!
I feel a lot better now.
Let's go, Uguisu.
Yeah.
Lilly, where are you?
What's that thing?
Maybe it's the exit! Let's check it out!
There!
No!
I was just in time.
Huh? We're back.
Thank goodness.
Hey!
There you are. I've been looking all over!
Teacher! Where did you go?
That's what I'd like to ask you.
Would you like to resume your magic training?
I think I'll pass.
Besides, I feel like I improved a bit.
I see. That's good to hear.
Then I shall take you home.
Goodbye, Teacher!
No more entering stranger's gardens, okay?
Very well.
Later!
Goodness.
Though, it truly was a beautiful garden.
Attention, please!
That was perfect!
Good work...
Lilly?
What are you here for?
You don't have any work today.
Just wanted to see you all, I guess.
Did something happen?
A lot.
It was just... crazy! So much stuff happened!
Like what?
That, I can't really say.
Huh?
It's fine.
What's wrong?
It was rough.
I see...
But I'm glad you came!
I have good news for you and Lulu!
What is it?
What could it be?
You see... You'll never guess what it is...
Out with it already.
We've set up a concert for you!
A concert...?
It'll be just you two, Lilly and Lulu.
Just us two?
A concert?!
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
It's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
(My dream!)
I just wanna know what the future holds
(Alone!)
Even if the stars in a moonless sky
Still twinkle
(No magic!)
Even if the clouds in a sunless sky
Still drift
I feel so lonely
(I was always right beside you)
I'm searching for you
I'll frame a photo of us two and hang it up
Let's set things the way we want, the way we will, the way they are
Take our chemistry, plus+, minus-, multiplied×, divided÷ by...
I love it every way
Calling me, calling you
(And you)
I want to walk up the stairs of the future with you
Lucky lucky shiny, our beating hearts dreamin' away
If there's clear skies tomorrow, everything will be okay
Maybe I'm a bit sad and weak
(But I'm happy!)
But when I'm with you I feel safe
There's no such thing as wasted time
Let's wait until the rain stops
Check it out, look up at the sky
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
That's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
What kind of future will the spotlight shine on?
Cinderella with a Curfew